Young man, there's no need to feel down
I said, young man, pick yourself off the ground
I said, young man, 'cause you're in a new town
There's no need to be unhappy
Young man, there's a place you can go
I said, young man,
when you're short on your dough
You can stay there
and I'm sure you will find
Many ways to have a good time
It's fun to stay at the YMCA
They have everything for young men to enjoy,
You can hang out with all the boys
It's fun to stay at the YMCA
You can get yourself clean, you can have a good meal
You can do whatever you feel
Young man, are you listening to me?
I said, young man, what do you wanna be?
I said, young man, you can make real your dreams
but you got to know this one thing.
No man does it all by himself.
I said, young man, put your pride on the shelf,
And just go there, to the Y.M.C.A.
I'm sure they can help you today
It's fun to stay at the YMCA
They have everything for young men to enjoy,
You can hang out with all the boys
It's fun to stay at the YMCA
You can get yourself clean, you can have a good meal
You can do whatever you feel
Young man, I was once in your shoes.
I said, I was down and out with the blues
I felt no man cared if I were alive
I felt the whole world was so jive
That's when someone came up to me
And said, "Young man, take a walk up the street
It’s a place there called the 'Y.M.C.A.'
They can start you back on your way."
It's fun to stay at the YMCA
They have everything for young men to enjoy,
You can hang out with all the boys
YMCA
It's fun to stay at the YMCA
Young man, young man, there's no need to feel down
Young man, young man, get yourself off the ground
YMCA
It's fun to stay at the YMCA